<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FaceControl</string>

    <string name="intro_1">
Welcome to FaceControl!\n\n
	This is an accessibility application designed to help users who have difficulty using tablet/smartphone (for example due to cerebral palsy or quadriplegia).\n
FaceControl works by enabling users to control their device using \'switches\'.\n\n
	Primary feature of FaceControl is that it uses camera switches, which means you can fully control
your Android device using facial gestures: with a smile, eyebrow raise, eye movement, eye wink, and mouth open.\n
		(for example you smile briefly, and then stop smiling)\n\n
		<a href="http://www.obstino.org/facecontrol/privacy.html">Privacy policy</a>\n\n
		<a href="http://www.obstino.org/facecontrol/eula.html">EULA</a>
    </string>

	<string name="intro_2">
	With FaceControl, you can also use physical switches that connect to the Android device using either Bluetooth or USB (such as from AbleNet, Enabling Devices, RJ Cooper, and Tecla).\n
An external keyboard or buttons on your Android device may also act as a switch.\n
In order to control your device using switches, you assign switch to a certain switch action.\n\n
	Two primary switch actions in FaceControl are: \n
1) "Select item/Scan" switch action \n
2) "Next item/Menu" action \n\n
You use these two switch actions to select a point on which to tap/drag, and to navigate through menu items.\n\n
	</string>

	<string name="intro_3">
	FaceControl also has a \"Sensitivity &amp; test\" menu where you can see yourself in the camera.\n
This is where you can test if the app detects your facial gestures (smile, eyebrow raise, eye look left/right, eye wink, and mouth open)\n
For example when you smile, a smiley face icon will appear, giving you direct feedback that a smile was recognized.\n\n
Additionally, you can also set sensitivity for all facial gestures, to optimize your experience.\n\n
		Before attempting to use the application, we strongly suggest you use this menu to get familiar with how
FaceControl recognizes facial gestures.
	</string>


</resources>